Hey Ankur Goswami, I welcome you all to
this platform of BFSi Careers 247
and as you all say that sir, please bring the
job opportunity of our city, so I have
told you earlier also that I am trying my best now, I
always used to do it earlier and I am still doing it,
job opportunity of small cities,
small cities means apart from Delhi NCR,
apart from metro cities, right, so
I try my best in whichever city it is, if I do
n't get it then I make whatever I get,
today I have got a
great opportunity for Dhanbad location,
but
before knowing about this opportunity, I will
say the same thing which I always say, there is a platform on the channel,
friends, this is a platform,
explore the platform, understand
what is there in the platform, go to the live section, go to the
playlist and see what you provide, I
take career guidance sessions for two-three hours, right,
apart from this, I will tell you about the entire job opportunity,
where are the interviews,
where are the jobs, where are the jobs
for the job  Vacancies have come
for 12th pass, what is there in BPOs, what is there
in multinational companies,
what is there in banks?  What is in finance companies
?  I bring you verified work from home
opportunities.
So I want you to join this channel.
Work on your over skills.
Develop yourself and share the channel.
Subscribe to the channel.  Friends,
join this platform.
Please subscribe to the platform.  Let's talk about
ICICI LBRD company which is a part of ICICI, in a
way it is the subsidiary of ICICI,
see when there are banks then the
main bank will only do banking activities.  There is
a part of the bank which
deals in insurance.  One will
deal in life insurance.  There is one who will
deal in medical insurance.
Each bank will have a part which will
deal with your demat account etc.
Right?  It is called securities.  Similarly,
this Lombard of ICICI
deals in medical insurance.
Correct?  So there are vacancies in ICICI LBA in Dhanbad.
And here it is written
Prefers Women Candidates.  So prefer
women candidates.  Women candidates
must apply for this.  You will
get an opportunity and you will definitely get a call.  I am
not saying that women should not do men, men should
not do men.  I am not saying this at all.
Preference is given.  Preference means
majority.  If 10 people are going, then out of
10, four will be boys and six will be
girls.  This is what it means.
Ok?  Let's move ahead.  Let's see
what are the requirements in this, friends.  A
minimum experience of one year is required.
You should have one year of experience in the field of sales, that is, as a
sales officer.
So definitely you are eligible.  Right?
And what do you have to do?  How will you apply this
?  Look here again to apply.
Your proper email ID is
given here Chaman.
ici lmbard.com right you have to mail on this email ID.  Those who have
experience, first prepare your resume very well because
one year of experience is required here.
Friends, what experience do you guys have
?  You write that I have one year of
experience in this bank.  That's it.  It is
not written like this.  Your resume will never be selected in life.
Go to description.  There is a video on how
to make a resume.  You must
definitely look for a professionally written resume.  There
is an application named Cwa.  There is a software called Cwa
through which you can easily make it very good.
But I have explained the method
in the video.  Must watch.  Once you see it,
take that resume and mail it here.  You have to send
mail to this mail ID.
What's the mail to do?  Remember this.  Have to mail.  Like
I said earlier.  Write in the subject line:
Regarding Job Opportunity.  And
then after that write Hi Chaman, meaning is there any
sir?  Hi Sir This is regarding a job
opportunity as I am looking for a job
kindly consider my profile.  Friends, let me
tell you one thing.  I am always trying to do something great for the children
and I keep doing it.
Whatever I tell you to write an email,
in every video I can give you in return.  I
can guarantee you.  No one will
tell.  No one tells.  I will tell you, forget it, no
one tells you.  Right?  So at
least join this channel for this very thing.  Make the channel
reach as many people as possible who are not able to get employment.   This is what I
believe.  I
want to end employment and unemployment.  I want to
bring employment.  So for that, your
help is very much needed.  So
subscribe to the channel.  Look here, it
is properly written here that you have to
send the review.  Write a resume.  Then
what is your current CTC?  How much CTC are you
expecting?  What is the notice period
?  What is location preference?
Ok?  So this is for Dhanbad.  I
would like you to definitely apply.  I would
say that even if you are from some other city, what is the harm
in applying once
?  What's going into mailing?  Please mail me.
Maybe some connection will emerge.  Right?
Remember, the biggest way to get a job is to find a job.
If you have
any contact number and email ID then it is a
great panacea for you.  So
make good use of it.  Okay friends?
Well, I will just say this, please do apply.
And graduation is required in this.
Graduation means graduation should be
completed in any stream
and should have one year experience.
Your salary is Rs 2.5 lakh to Rs 5.5 lakh per
annum.  It will depend on what your last
salary is.  Ok?  Let's thank
you so much everyone.  This is also a sales profile.  It
is a good profile.  It's fun.  You will enjoy it.
I would just say keep moving forward.
Keep working on your work skills and
join me.  I will again
bring some career guidance session.  And see you
in another job update.  Take care of yourself
and I wish you all success.   Get
settled somewhere as soon as possible and
start your life.  Thank you so much.  Take
care.  See you in the next job update.